Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups, 59621
  - Subseries I.B. Individuals and Family Groups: Medium Format
    - Webster, Daniel (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Webster, Horace (Drawer Medium)
    - Webster, J. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Webster, Noah (Drawer Medium)
    - Weddell, Peter M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Weed, Nathaniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Weed, Stephen H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Weeks, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Weightman, George CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Welch, Bartholomew G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Weld, Angelina Grimke (Drawer Medium)
    - Welles, Gideon (Drawer Medium)
    - Wellington, Duke of (Drawer Medium)
    - Wells, Charlotte Fowler (Drawer Medium)
    - Wells, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Wells, John D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wells, S. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wells, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Wentworth, W. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Werner, Adolph (Drawer Medium)
    - Wesigar, David Addison (Drawer Medium)
    - Wessels, Henry Walton (Drawer Medium)
    - West, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - West, Joseph Rodman (Drawer Medium)
    - West, Louisa Barker (Drawer Medium)
    - Wetherill, John M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wetmore, Prosper M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wharton (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Wharton, Deborah
      Wharton, G. M.
      Wharton, Gabriel C.
      Wharton, Samuel
      Wharton, T. L.
    - Wheaton, Frank (Drawer Medium)
    - Wheeler, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Wheeler, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Whipple, Henry [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Whipple, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Whipple, William Denison (Drawer Medium)
    - White (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      White [crossed out]
      White, Andrew D. [crossed out]
      White, E. J.
      White, Edward D.
      White, Edward S.
      White, Henry
      White, Henry Kirke CCNY
      White, Julius
      White, Roy B.
      White, William
    - Whitefield (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitehouse, Norman de R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Whiteside, J. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitfield, W. E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitman, C. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitman, Walt (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitney, O. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitney, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Whitson, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Whittier, John Greenleaf (Drawer Medium)
    - Whittingham, William Rollinson [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Wickersham, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wickham, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Wickham, William Carter (Drawer Medium)
    - Wickham, William H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wiggers, Johanna (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilberforce, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilberforce, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilcocks, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilcox, Cadmus Marcellus (Drawer Medium)
    - Wildey, Thoman (Drawer Medium)
    - Wiley, Ephraim E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilhelmj, August (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilkez, G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilkie, D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilkins, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Wilkinson (Drawer Medium)
    - Young, Whitney, Jr. (Drawer Medium)
  - Subseries I.C. Individuals and Family Groups: Large Format
    - Adams, John Quincy (Drawer Large)
    - Alger, Russell A. (Drawer Large)
    - Arbuckle, M. (Drawer Large)
    - Arista, M. (Drawer Large)
    - Arthur, Chester A. (Drawer Large)
    - Banks, Nathaniel P. (Drawer Large)
    - Beach, Moses Yale (Drawer Large)
    - Beaureguard, G. T. (Drawer Large)
    - Beecher, Henry Ward (Drawer Large)
    - Blaine, James G. (Drawer Large)
    - Blair, Frank P. (Drawer Large)
    - Brant, Joseph (get from T file) (Drawer Large)
    - Brewster, William (Drawer Large)
    - Bricker, John W. (Drawer Large)
    - Brodhead, John Romeyn (Drawer Large)
    - Brooke, J. R. (Drawer Large)
    - Brown, John (Drawer Large)
    - Bruce, M. Linn (Drawer Large)
    - Buchanan, James (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Burnside, Ambrose E. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Butler, Benjamin F. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Carroll, John (Drawer Large)
    - Calhoun, John C. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Chapin, E. H. (Drawer Large)
    - Clay, Henry (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Cleveland, Grover (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Cobbett, William (Drawer Large)
    - Columbus, Christopher (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Conwell, Russell H. (Drawer Large)
    - Copeland, Royal S. (Drawer Large)
    - Crockett, Davy (Drawer Large)
    - Crook, George (Drawer Large)
    - Curtis, B. R. (Drawer Large)
    - Custer, George A. (Drawer Large)
    - Davis, Jefferson (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Day, Benjamin H. (Drawer Large)
    - Delancey, William Heathcote (Drawer Large)
    - Delany, Martin (Drawer Large)
    - Dewey, George, and wife (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Drawer Large)
    - Dickens, Charles (Drawer Large)
    - Dickinson, Daniel S. (Drawer Large)
    - Dix, John A. (Drawer Large)
    - Douglas, Stephen A. (Drawer Large)
    - Douglass, Frederick (Drawer Large)
    - Durand, Asher B. (Drawer Large)
    - Dwight, Amos T. (Drawer Large)
    - Edison, Thomas A. (Drawer Large)
    - Elder, John A. (Drawer Large)
    - Ellice, Edward (Drawer Large)
    - Ericsson, John (Drawer Large)
    - Evans, Robert D. (Drawer Large)
    - Everett, Edward (Drawer Large)
    - Ewell, Richard S. (Drawer Large)
    - Fairbanks, Charles W. (Drawer Large)
    - Fenton, Reuben E. (Drawer Large)
    - Fillmore, Millard (Drawer Large)
    - Flower, Roswell P. (Drawer Large)
    - Foch, Ferdinand (Drawer Large)
    - Forrest, Catherine Norton (Drawer Large)
    - Forrest, Nathaniel B. (Drawer Large)
    - Franklin, Benjamin (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Franklin, William B. (Drawer Large)
    - Fremont, John C. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Fry, Charles M. [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Fulton, Robert (Drawer Large)
    - Funston, Frederick (Drawer Large)
    - Furness, W. H. (Drawer Large)
    - Gardiner, John Lyon (Drawer Large)
    - Garfield, James A. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Garibaldi (Drawer Large)
    - Gomez, Maximo (Drawer Large)
    - Gracie, James King [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Grant, Frederick Dent (Drawer Large)
    - Grant, Ulysses S. (Drawer Large)
      Portraits in plain clothes (separate folder)
      Portraits in uniform (separate folder)
      Memorials (separate folder)
    - Greeley, Horace (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Grey, Jane, Lady (Drawer Large)
    - Greene, Nathanael (Drawer Large)
    - Griffith, David Reese (Drawer Large)
    - Haig, Douglas (Drawer Large)
    - Hale, Nathan (Drawer Large)
    - Halleck, Henry W. (Drawer Large)
    - Hamilton, Alexander (Drawer Large)
    - Hampton, Wade (Drawer Large)
    - Hancock, Winfield Scott (Drawer Large)
    - Harding, Warren G. (Drawer Large)
    - Harrison, William Henry (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Hasting, Thomas S. (Drawer Large)
    - Havelock, Henry (Drawer Large)
    - Hayes, Rutherford B. (Drawer Large)
    - Heintzelman, Samuel P. (Drawer Large)
    - Hill, Ambrose P. (Drawer Large)
    - Hobart, John Henry (Drawer Large)
    - Hobson, Richmond P. (Drawer Large)
    - Hooker, Joseph (Drawer Large)
    - Houston, Samuel (Drawer Large)
    - Howard, Oliver O. (Drawer Large)
    - Howland, Mrs. Henry Elias (Drawer Large)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans (Drawer Large)
    - Hull, Isaac (Drawer Large)
    - Hunter, David (Drawer Large)
    - Hutton, Mancius S. (Drawer Large)
    - Irving, Washington (Drawer Large)
    - Jackson, Andrew (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Jackson, Thomas J. "Stonewall" (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Drawer Large)
    - Johnson, Andrew (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Johnston, A. S. (Drawer Large)
    - Johnston, John Taylor (Drawer Large)
    - Johnston, Joseph E. (Drawer Large)
    - Kearney, Philip (Drawer Large)
    - Kemble, Fanny (Drawer Large)
    - Kennan, George (Drawer Large)
    - Kent, James (Drawer Large)
    - Killpatrick, Judson (Drawer Large)
    - Kosciuszko, Tadeusz (Drawer Large)
    - Kossuth, Louis (Drawer Large)
    - Lafayette (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Laurens, Henry (Drawer Large)
    - Lawton, H. W. (Drawer Large)
    - Lee, Fitzhugh (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Lee, Robert E. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (Drawer Large)
      Deathbed scenes
      Memorial and Allegorical prints
      Memorial and Reward broadsides
      Photomechanical Reproductions
      ....Bearded (3 folders) [half, full, and bust length]
      ....Beardless
      ....Groups
      ........With Family
      ........With Generals
      ........With McClellan and Garrett
    - Locke, G. E. (Drawer Large)
    - Loffan, William M. (Drawer Large)
    - Logan, John (Drawer Large)
    - Longfellow, Henry W. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Longstreet, James (Drawer Large)
    - Lyon, Nathaniel (Drawer Large)
    - McClellan, George B., General (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - McKinley, William (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - McPherson, James B. (Drawer Large)
    - Manks, Richard (Drawer Large)
    - Marsh, Clarissa Seymour (Drawer Large)
    - Meade, George G. (Drawer Large)
    - Merritt, Wesley (Drawer Large)
    - Miles, Nelson A. (Drawer Large)
    - Milledoler, Philip (Drawer Large)
    - Monroe, James (Drawer Large)
    - Moore, Benjamin (Drawer Large)
    - Moore, Eli (Drawer Large)
    - Morgan, John (Drawer Large)
    - Morris, Robert (Drawer Large)
    - Morse, Samuel F. B. (Drawer Large)
    - Morton, Levi P. (Drawer Large)
    - Mount, William Sidney (Drawer Large)
    - Napoleon (death mask) (Drawer Large)
    - Nelson, Samuel (Drawer Large)
    - Nye, Edgar W. (see James Whitcomb Riley) (Drawer Large)
    - Ord, E. O. C. (Drawer Large)
    - Osterhaus, Peter J. (Drawer Large)
    - Otis, Elwell S. (Drawer Large)
    - Parker, Peter (Drawer Large)
    - Pasteur, Louis (Drawer Large)
    - Penn, William (Drawer Large)
    - Petain, Henri (Drawer Large)
    - Pierce, Franklin (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Pitt, William (Drawer Large)
    - Potter, Alonzo (Drawer Large)
    - Pratt, Zadock (Drawer Large)
    - Price, Sterling (Drawer Large)
    - Priestly, Joseph (Drawer Large)
    - Pruyn, Robert H. [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Reynolds, General (Drawer Large)
    - Riley, James Whitcomb (Drawer Large)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin (Drawer Large)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Rosecrans, William S. (Drawer Large)
    - Sampson, William Thompson (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Schley, Winfield Scott (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Schofield, John M. (Drawer Large)
    - Schuyler, Philip Jeremiah (Drawer Large)
    - Scott, Walter (Drawer Large)
    - Scott, Winfield (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Sedgwick, John (Drawer Large)
    - Seymour, Molly Marsh (Drawer Large)
    - Seymour, Moses (Drawer Large)
    - Seymour, Thomas Youngs (Drawer Large)
    - Shafter, W. R. (Drawer Large)
    - Sherwood, George E. (Drawer Large)
    - Sheridan, Philip H. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Sherman, William T. (Drawer Large)
    - Sigel, Franz (Drawer Large)
    - Sigsbee, Charles D. (Drawer Large)
    - Sims William S. (Drawer Large)
    - Stoneman, George (Drawer Large)
    - Stotsenburg, John M. (Drawer Large)
    - Stuart, Gilbert (Drawer Large)
    - Stuart, James E. B. (Drawer Large)
    - Stuyvesant, Peter (Drawer Large)
    - Sulzer, William (Drawer Large)
    - Sumner, Charles (Drawer Large)
    - Taft, Alphonso [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Talmage, T. DeWitt (Drawer Large)
    - Tarleton, Banastre (Drawer Large)
    - Taylor, Zachary (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Tell, William (Drawer Large)
    - Thomas, George H. (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Tieck, Ludwig (Drawer Large)
    - Tilghman, William (Drawer Large)
    - Townshend, George (Drawer Large)
    - Tracy, Edward [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Trimble, George T. [crossed out] (Drawer Large)
    - Trobriand, Regis de (Drawer Large)
    - Twain, Mark (Drawer Large)
    - Tweed, William M. (Drawer Large)
    - Tyler, John (Drawer Large)
    - Tyson, Elisha (Drawer Large)
    - Van Amringe, J. H. (Drawer Large)
    - Van Buren, Martin (Drawer Large)
    - Wainwright, John Howard (Drawer Large)
    - Washington, George (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
      Certificates and Penmanship Exercises
      Deathbed Scenes
      Monuments
      ....after LeMire
      ....after LePaon
      ........Busts (2 folders)
      ........Full Length
      ........Landsdown, portrait
      ........Busts
      ........Full length
      ........Groups
      ............With Family
      ............With Mother
      ....Military situations (incl. Evacuation Day)
    - Washington, Martha (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Watson, John C. (Drawer Large)
    - Wayne, Anthony (Drawer Large)
    - Webster, Daniel (separate folder) (Drawer Large)
    - Webster, Noah (Drawer Large)
    - Weir, Robert Walter (Drawer Large)
    - Weitzel, Godfrey (Drawer Large)
    - Wheeler, Joseph (Drawer Large)
    - White, William (Drawer Large)
    - Willis, Nathaniel P. (Drawer Large)
    - Wilson, Woodrow (Drawer Large)
    - Wool, John E. (Drawer Large)
  - Subseries I.D. Individuals and Family Groups: Oversize Format
    - Andrews, George Pierce (Drawer Oversize)
    - Blaine, James G. (Drawer Oversize)
    - Clay, Henry (Drawer Oversize)
    - Eugenie, Empress, consort of Napoleon III, Emperor of the French (Drawer Oversize)
    - Franklin, Benjamin (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
    - Grant, Ulysses S. (Drawer Oversize)
    - Harrison, William Henry (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
    - Lee, Robert E. (Drawer Oversize)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
      With Cabinet
    - McGlynn, Edward (Drawer Oversize)
    - McKinley, William (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
    - Montgomery, Richard (Drawer Oversize)
    - Napoleon, Emperor of the French (Drawer Oversize)
    - Scott, Winfield (Drawer Oversize)
    - Sherman, William T. (Drawer Oversize)
    - Trump, Tom (Drawer Oversize)
    - Washington, George (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
      ....With Family
      Inaugural Centennial
      ....Inauguration and ball scenes
    - Webster, Daniel (separate folder) (Drawer Oversize)
  - Subseries I.E. Men of Affairs
    - Men of Affairs (copy 1; bound) (Box [157])
      From the library of Samuel V. Hoffman with name stamped in gold on front cover.
      001) Samuel V. Hoffman
      002) Otto R. Hartman
      003) C. E. Finney
      004) Jules Hurtig
      005) John C. Wickman
      006) J. H. Woods
      007) Abraham L. Newman
      008) Sig. Hirsh
      009) Dr. E. E. Cady
      010) John F. Flood
      011) Chas. Polifeme
      012) N. Brigham Hall
      013) William H. Amerman
      014) Jno. F. Felley
      015) E. M. Tierney
      016) A. J. Peyton
      017) Jno. F. Hemenway
      018) Jno. A. Murray
      019) Stuart Duncan
      020) D. Arnould
      021) Joseph Huber
      022) Louis Frazin
      023) Wilbur J. Follett
      024) Geo. A Varnet
      025) E. P. Richhelm
      026) Frank Zotti
      027) Isadore D. Morrison
      028) Chas. Sandstrom
      029) J. C. Seager
      030) Julian Benedict
      031) Humphries O'Sullivan
      032) Marcelino Perez
      033) Gustave Helmstetter
      034) Pat H. McCarren
      035) Wm. B. Proctor
      036) James L. Libbey
      037) Herman Simon
      038) R. W. Buckley
      039) C. H. Van Buren
      040) Dr. Geo. B. Win
      041) Willis W. Russell
      042) Adolph C. Hottenroth
      043) Maurice B. Mendham
      044) H. Nathen
      045) Julius Lambert
      046) Tunis G. Bergen
      047) Chas. R. Bowen
      048) Sigmund Rosenwald
      049) Newton Bennington
      050) J. Park Channing
      051) Roland R. Conklin
      052) Geo. F. Chamberlin
      053) Thomas E. Rush
      054) Thomas F. Somers
      055) A. G. Kaufmann
      056) Harlen N. Whipple
      057) J. Hatfield Morton
      058) William H. Miller
      059) Jno. I. Underhill
      060) N. A. L. Lattard
      061) Arthur P. Heinze
      062) Abraham Oberstein
      063) Chas. F. Prentice
      064) Augustus J. Kitz
      065) Jon Dunston
      066) Theron L. Cannan
      067) H. L. Moxley
      068) Miller Reese Hutchinson
      069) Chas. R. Saul
      070) Dr. H. W. Guilshan
      071) Maurice Bamberger
      072) Prof. Anthony Barker
      073) Hugo Jaeckel
      074) Adam A. Cross
      075) Chas. Shongood
      076) William Wills
      077) Chas. F. Noyes
      078) Lew Fields
      079) Clifford L. Miller
      080) Dr. C. S. Levy
      081) M. A. Dananbaum
      082) Col. Alvaro Garcia
      083) Peter T. Austin
      084) Rastus S. Sansom
      085) F. G. Schmidt
      086) Harvey A. Patterson
      087) Thomas A. Ennis
      088) Gus Hill
      089) A. M. Powell
      090) Myron W. Robinson
      091) W. P. Callaghan
      092) R. Floyd Clarke
      093) I. H. Rosenfeld
      094) Painless Parker
      095) Dr. E. F. Hanks
      096) G. F. Peck
      097) Dr. Andrew Linn-Nelden
      098) Franklin D. Mooney
      099) David Thornton
      100) Geo. Tyler
      101) E. C. M. Fitzgerald
      102) A. D. Proctor-Smith
      103) William Durland
      104) Jno. W Merriman
      105) Geo. L. Strong
      106) Dr. Chas. W. Miller
      107) Vellette F. Pelletreau [William S. Pelletreau?]
      108) Abram I. Elkus
      109) Reginald H. Sayre, M.D.
      110) Chas. F. Wetzel
      111) Frank T. Huntoon
      112) Theodore Mundorf
      113) William Scheer
      114) D. Auerbach
      115) Maurice Joyce
      116) J. E. Dodsen
      117) Wm. Gardiner
      118) G. L. Boissevein
      119) Edw. A. Alexander
      120) A. M. A. Richardson
      121) Cesare Conti
      122) F. R. McKenzie
      123) Jno. P. Kirwin 124) Chas. Huell
      125) Waldo G. Morse
      126) W. H. Acken
      127) L. Wesley Spear
      128) Chas. Trieler
      129) Jon F. Brush
      130) G. Tuoti
      131) John Love Elliot
      132) Morris Berman
      133) J. Hollis Wells
      134) Samuel F. Meyers
      135) Eugene N. Foss
      136) J. Chas. Weschler
      137) Jaques Rosenberg
      138) Henry J. Pain
      139) Wm. Salomon
      140) Peter Zucker
      141) Matthew Rock
      142) Thomas Simpson
      143) Andrew J. Murphy
      144) J. R. Clark
      145) Jno. A. Wilbur
      146) Herman Raub
      147) David C. Meyers
      148) J. H. Mansfield
      149) Matthew I. Fox
      150) Andrew J. Cobe
      151) Thos. P. Fitzsimmons
      152) J. F. Blanchard
      153) Dr. A. H. Swinburne
      154) Wm. H. Llewellyn
      155) A. P. Morrison
      156) N. G. Hitchcock
      157) Simon Batt
      158) L. C. Mouquin
      159) Col. B. Baggot
      160) James Ahearn
      161) Geo. H. Proctor
      162) T. Benton Ackerson
      163) Antonio Zucca
      164) Frank A. Acer
      165) Edwin N. Doll
      166) Frederick St. John
      167) W. Wayne Belvin
      168) Frederick Seymour
      169) Jon E. Eustis
      170) John W. Cottrell
      171) Jerome H. Renick
      172) George Ryall
      173) K. Mandell
      174) J. S. A. Wittke
      175) J. H. Kamping
      176) James P. Mulhern
      177) David C. Webb
      178) Oscar Sherer
      179) A. Sanford Adler
      180) Louis Steckler
      181) Robert Maynicke
      182) H. C. Peters
      183) J. Noah H. Slee
      184) Henry D. Cochrance
      185) Dan Mason
    - Men of Affairs (copy 2; loose plates) (Box [158])
      Part of cover lacking, with loss of part of name on cover ("Louis A. Ha[...]").
      001) W. I. Lincoln Adams
      002) John J. Armory
      003) A. A. Anderson
      004) Jno. E. Andrus
      005) Clarence D. Ashley
      006) Frederick F. Ayer
      007) Jules S. Bache
      008) Henry Clinton Backus
      009) Leroy W. Baldwin
      010) J. C. Barclay
      011) F. H. Barnaby
      012) Lindow W. Bates
      013) James Gordon Battle
      014) Geo. D. Beattys
      015) Chas. E. Blaney
      016) John A. Bensel
      017) Geo. E. Best
      018) Wm. H. Birkmire
      019) Dan Bindsall
      020) Judge Henry Bischoff
      021) Geo. M. Booth
      022) H. H. Bowman
      023) Henry A. Budd
      024) A. N. Burbank
      025) Frank Butterworth
      026) Thos. Byrnes
      027) Willard L. Candee
      028) John Carstengen
      029) Fred T. Chandler
      030) Lewis Stuyvesant Chanler
      031) Capt. Arthur H. Clark
      032) Geo. C. Clausen
      033) Robt. C. Clowry
      034) Jos. B. Coghlan
      035) Bird S. Coler
      036) Henry Corn
      037) E. L. Corthall
      038) Michael J. Dady
      039) Elliot Danforth
      040) Thos. Darlington
      041) J. Vipond Davies
      042) Chauncey M. Depew
      043) Evans R. Dick
      044) John R. Dos Passos
      045) Robert E. Dowling
      046) Jno. F. Dryden
      047) John W. Dunn
      048) Geo. R. Dyer
      049) Thos. A. Edison
      050) Beethoven Englander
      051) Newman Erb
      052) Henry D. Estabrook
      053) Judge A. B. Fall
      054) Edward H. Fallows
      055) Pliny Fisk
      056) Ashbel P. Fitch
      057) John H. Flagler
      058) Julius Fleischman
      059) Anson R. Flower
      060) Thomas J. Foster
      061) B. Y. Frost
      062) James W. Gerard Jr.
      063) W. E. G. Gaillard
      064) David Gerber
      065) Saml. H. Guggenheimer
      066) Solomon R. Guggenheim
      067) Geo. C. Gill
      068) Jno. N. Golding
      069) Geo. J. Gould
      070) Howard Gould
      071) George S. Graham
      072) William C. Greene
      073) Abraham Gruber
      074) Isaac Guggenheim
      075) Wm. Guggenheim
      076) J. Temple Gwathmey
      077) Henry H. Hall
      078) Nathaniel Haven
      079) Job E. Hedges
      080) B. A. Hegeman Jr.
      081) W. C. Heppenheimer
      082) Hugo Hirsh
      083) Isaac Hopper
      084) J. M. Horton
      085) Otto Horwitz
      086) J. E. Hulshizer
      087) H. E. Huntington
      088) Chas. M. Jacobs
      089) Adrian H. Joline
      090) E. Clarence Jones
      091) Francis W. Jones
      092) Richard W. Jones Jr.
      093) John H. Judge
      094) John C. Juhring
      095) John P. Kane
      096) John Kean
      097) James R. Keene
      098) E. J. Kehoe
      099) Bryan L. Kennelly
      100) J. Bene King
      101) H. B. Kirk
      102) Gustav H. Kissel
      103) Edward Lauterbach
      104) Chas. Lanier
      105) J. Edgar Leycraft
      106) Chas. W Mackey
      107) W. P. Maloney
      108) W. G. McAdoo
      109) Edward E. McCall
      110) John McCullogh
      111) Thos. A. McIntyre
      112) Wm. W. McLaughlin
      113) Herman A. Metz
      114) John Miles
      115) Harry B. Mingle
      116) Robt. R.Moore
      117) M. L. Morgenthau
      118) Chas. Griffith Moses
      119) Thos. M. Mulvy
      120) W. D. Munson
      121) Franklin Murphy
      122) A. Milton Napier
      123) Henry E. Nesmith
      124) Ludwig Nisson
      125) J. Van Vechten Olcott
      126) R. Morgan Olcott
      127) Geo. R. Olney
      128) R. S. O'Loughlin
      129) Richard F. Pettigrew
      130) Fred Pflomm
      131) Ira A. Place
      132) Thos. C. Platt
      133) Theodore Prince
      134) Henry S. Redmond
      135) Jordon J. Rollins
      136) John B. Rose
      137) Walter W. Ross
      138) W. J. Salomon
      139) Samuel S. Sanford
      140) Isaac N. Seligman
      141) Harry C. Senior
      142) Dr. Newton M. Shaffer
      143) Clarence J. Shearn
      144) James R. Sheffield
      145) Henry F. Shoemaker
      146) Chas. Sooy Smith
      147) Fred Southback
      148) James Speyer
      149) H. G. Squires
      150) John Stanton
      151) Louis Stern
      152) Fred C. Stevens
      153) W. L. Stow
      154) Nevada S. Stranahan